Hi.
It's dawn in Korea.
I had something spicy.
I have runny nose.
Hi.
There are four people.
Four people came in.
Hi.
It's morning in Korea.
Morning?
We finished our first day in England.
Second day.
We're out of our mind.
The second day.
The first day.
We finished.
Before I remove my makeup,
I turned on the camera to do a live.
It's our first time in Europe.
I was a little worried.
I didn't expect the reaction.
It's our first time in Europe.
People sang along to our song.
They made it really loud, so I can't hear it well.
You didn't have to worry about it at all.
That's right. It was so much fun.
And at the end, I'm looking forward to it.
Video? Fans' video?
They made it so well.
Yeah, I think so.
They sing well, too.
That's right. That's right.
I sang Moonlight today.
Is it spicy?
Yeah, it's too spicy.
I was hungry after the performance, so I ate something.
I'm going to have a late-night snack.
You got up really early.
That's right. What time is it in Korea now?
What did you eat?
I ate the catering.
Tofu kimchi and...
It's a little past 10 o'clock in London.
10 p.m.
Oh, it's 6 o'clock in the morning.
Oh, it's 6 o'clock in the morning?
It's 6 o'clock in the morning.
You got up early.
It's the weekend now.
That's right.
No, I'm doing a live.
Now...
I really want to come back to England again.
Yeah, I really wanted to come back.
I could only see the outside in the car, so I was a little sad.
It was so pretty.
The building?
Yeah, that's right.
It's so pretty and the weather is warmer than I thought.
That's right.
I thought it would be nice to take a walk.
But I'm not lying.
I've never stepped on the ground outside.
Really.
I've never stepped on it since I came to England.
Airport, hotel, concert hall.
Like this.
I didn't even go to a convenience store or a mart.
Next time, we're going to...
Where are we going?
France.
We're going to France.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Bonjour.
I have to get ready to go out, but I'm not ready for Bubble Live.
I'm going to be late.
What day is it today?
Are we going to hang out?
What day is it in Korea?
Is it Saturday in Korea?
Is this Friday?
Saturday morning at 6.40?
Is it Saturday, September 9th?
It's already September 9th?
I think it was yesterday, September 1st.
It's already September 9th.
Chuseok is coming soon.
It's been over a week since September 1st.
I know.
Chuseok is coming soon.
October...
We have something in October.
It's very important.
Where are you going all of a sudden?
Don't go!
My head...
I can't hear you.
What's so amazing is that
ONCEs know my nickname.
British ONCEs.
I was so surprised.
I was so touched.
How do you know?
It was so amazing.
I was so happy.
How are you?
I'm fine.
It was so fun.
I had so much fun during the concert.
The response was so...
The response was so big.
They sang along with me.
I was so touched.
Especially the last video
that our fans made for us.
I was so touched.
I think I should go wash up now.
See you again.
Thank you for today.
Thank you.
See you again.
Bye.